

# **Kaho Cheng**

- ✓ chengy1989@hotmail.com
- ・ 豊島区,北大塚1-33-4,リヴォオツカ Ⅲ 7号室
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/kaho-cheng-19584b223/
- 09064951345
- k https://azusa89.github.io/portfolio\_site/
- https://github.com/Azusa89

#### **Profile**

"Hi there, my name is Kaho Cheng and I am a British-born Hong Kong person with a passion for 3D modeling and web development. I have experience working as a casino dealer and English teacher, and have spent many years honing my 3D modeling skills as a hobby. I am now looking to use my skills and experiences to pursue a career in web development and am excited to take on new challenges in this field."

#### Web Dev Skills

Html | Css | Javascript | Ruby on Rails | React Bootstap | Sass | Postgresql | Figma

### **Digital creatives**

3dsmax | Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Premier Adobe Illustrator | Blender | Zbrush

#### **Certificates**

- Le Wagon Fullstack Web Development
- Google IT support ☑
- Responsive Web Design ☑
- 1st degree BAHons Animation
- TEFL 120 hours

#### **Education**

Fullstack Web development, Le Wagon 12/2022 | Tokyo, Japan

**BaHons Animations,** *Sheffield Hallam* 06/2010 | Sheffield, UK

**Media studies,** *Durham New college* 06/2007 | Durham, UK

#### **Projects**

**Substracked,** Subscription tracker Final project from my time at Le Wagon

**Rent-a-Retro,** *Retro video game rentals* First group project at Le Wagon

# **Professional Experience**

**Head of English department,** Wisdom Academy

2021 - 2022 | Tokyo

Manage a team of English teachers between various schools.

Developing and building English curricilum.

Training new staff.

Work directly with the CEO on various aspects of running the company.

**Educator,** KidsUp

2019 - 2021 | Tokyo

English teaching to classes of up to 40 students. Training new staff on the OJT program.

**Dealer Inspector,** Park Lane Club

2015 - 2019 | London

Dealer and supervise high stakes games in a luxury environment

Dealer, Empire Casino

2012 - 2015 | London

Deal tables games such as BlackJack, roulette and poker.

## Languages

English

Japanese

Cantonese

• • • • •

